

HUYNH THANH TÙNG

Address: 239 Binh Loi Street, Ward 13, Binh Thanh District, HCMC

DOB: 27 Dec 1990

SUMMARY

I have over 5 years of exp. as a Team Leader, 3 years of exp. as a Backend Developer & 1 years of exp. as a Project Leader role. My goal is to become a Senior Backend Dev in the next 2 years.

I have software project implementation skills from analysis to development and implementation.

Having knowledge of development and release Mobile application, Website.

Having knowledge of eCommerce on Amazon, Ebay, Walmart, Shopify, USPS, UPS, Shipworks... Having programming skills and experience in developing Mobile application, Frontend, Backend, Setup server & maintenance services.

WORK EXPERIENCES

FREELANCER (04/2024 - Now)

FULL STACK DEVELOPER (The Room for Rent management website)

Team size: 1 members

- + Research & analyze customer requirements.
- + Building the management system website.
- + Setup hosting & domain to deploy code.
- + Develop modules: User, Room, Citizen, Contract, Invoice...
- + Services: Send Email, Task Scheduling, Generate PDF file...

Techs: Laravel 11, Bootstrap 5, jQuery, MySQL, Nice-Admin, Git, Google Office...

NEXACORN JSC (05/2022 - 03/2024)

PROJECT LEADER (The AI fashion shopping mobile application)

Team size: 11 members

- + Analyze & deploy project according to the Scrum model.
- + Manage, assign tasks, check & evaluate the work of the Developers and Testers.
- + Test and release the Mobile application on GooglePlay, AppStore.
- + Design the Database structure.
- + Design the API to serve Frontend, Backend & Mobile application.
- + Design the UI/UX for the Administrator website.
- + Setup & maintenance: Linux server (Ubuntu), Nginx, FTP, SSL, Redis cache server.
- + Setup & maintenance: Mongo DB, Mongo Atlas, MySQL server.
- + Setup TIG stack monitoring system (Telegraf Influxdb Grafana).

- + Manage to build the Company landing page
- + Configure the Crontab/Schedule on Linux, Windows.
- + Have knowledge of Firebase (in-app messaging, cloud messaging, remote config).
- + Have knowledge of Facebook API, GA4, ADJUST, Sentry.
- + Have knowledge of image analysis & comparison algorithms using Python algorithms.
- + Have knowledge of Vector DB (Pinecone).
- + Interviewing, recruiting.

Techs: Jira, ReactJS, ReactNative, Python, Selenium, Figma, Github, GA4, Adjust, Sentry, MongoDB, MongoAtlas, Codelgniter, NestJS, Redis Cache, Queue, Facebook Api, Firebase, Jenkins, Swagger, Postman, Google Office...

VITOX LLC (07/2020 - 12/2021)

PROJECT MANAGER (outsource)

Team size: 4 members

- + Building the management system for enterprises specializing in analyzing & assessing the quality of products circulating in the USA market that meet standards of Prop-65 CA.
- + Research & analyze customer requirements.
- + Planning to execute the project according to the Agile & Scrum model.
- + Perform server construction, configuration & project deployment.
- + Managing, checking & summarizing the tasks of team members.
- + Deploy project to production.

Techs: Laravel, VueJS, Git, Google Office, Trello...

HMD IT JSC (2015 - 2021)

TEAM LEADER

Team size: 7 members

- + Building a TA team to gather user requirements, research, analyze, deploy projects.
- + Building a QA team to perform software quality control & improvement.
- + Make a project implementation plan according to the requirements of the Management and the Board of Directors.
- + Analyze & deploy projects according to the Agile & Scrum model.
- + Manage, check & evaluate the work of the employees in the group.
- + Support superiors in orienting the development of the department in line with the company's direction.
- + Drafting technical documents, processes & regulations of the IT department.
- + Building Backend Business operating system.
- + Setup & maintenance server: Website, Api, Git Deploy...
- + Interviewing, recruiting.

Techs: Codelgniter, AngularJS, Laravel, VueJS, Git, Open Project, OneNote, Google Office...

UNILEVER VIETNAM (06/2017 - 06/2018)

BACKEND DEVELOPER (outsource)

- + Building Backend System which is the News, Gift, Product, Inventory, Order management and Report website...
- + Building API System to serve Frontend, Backend, Mobile.
- + Combine sending SMS to API System to execute OTP verification.
- + Support & maintenance system.

Techs: Codelgniter, AngularJS, Codelgniter & Restful API Extension, Git, Trello...

YES4ALL LLC (2013 - 2015)

BACKEND DEVELOPER

- + Building Backend System.
- + Building Business support modules:
 - o Purchasing, NPI, Logistics, Shipping...
 - o Personnel, Timesheet...

Techs: Codelgniter, Jquery, Joomla...

SOFT SKILLS

- + Management of Middle Managers MMM.
- + Have knowledge & skills in Project management based on Agile & Scrum model.
- + Participate in software architecture design & data structure.
- + Gather user requirements & perform analysis of the requirements.
- + Research & apply techniques that ensure user requirements.
- + Ability to communication skill, mindmap, brand storming, coaching & interview.

EDUCATION

Management of Middle Manager (MMM certificate)

Linux server, Mongo Atlas

Laravel, VueJS, Git

Python, AngularJS 1.x

TOEIC 500

PHP and MySQL Server Advance

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Networking

CCNA, MCSE

Hobbies & Interests:

- + Reading Books
- + Technology Research
- + Photography
- + Portable audio devices